Guide to the Frederick R. Koch Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Alphabetical Name List
  - Poulenc, Francis
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - Bérard, Christian. Drawing of Poulenc: pencil
        FRKF 927
  - Proust, Marcel
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Beaunier, André, [ca. 1912-1913] (Box 48, Folder 983)
        FRKF 173
        FRKF 529.1-2
      - Billy, Robert de, [ca. 1892-1919] (Box 48, Folder 984)
        FRKF 61
        FRKF 461.1-2
        FRKF 862
      - Binet-Valmer, [ca. 1921 Jun 4] (Box 48, Folder 985)
        FRKF 175
      - Boulenger, Jacques, [1921]-22 (Box 48, Folder 986)
        FRKF 208
        FRKF 209
        FRKF 210
        FRKF 211
        FRKF 730.1
        FRKF 740
      - Caraman-Chimay, Alexandre de, Princesse, [ca. 1903]-[ca. 1917], n.d. (Box 48, Folder 987)
        FRKF 673.1-3
      - Casa Fuerte, Illan de, [1903-07?], n.d. (Box 48, Folder 988)
        FRKF 252
        FRKF 1211
        FRKF 1377
      - Catusse, Marie-Marguerite Bertin, [1904-17] (Box 48, Folder 989)
        FRKF 194
        FRKF 969
        FRKF 982
      - Cazalis, Henri, [ca. 1906 Feb] (Box 48, Folder 990)
        FRKF 169
      - Cocteau, Jean (to Marcel), 1919 Aug 7 (Box 48, Folder 991)
        FRKF 1336
      - Daudet, Julia, [ca. 1909 Nov 19] (Box 48, Folder 992)
        FRKF 68
      - Daudet, Lucien, [1909 early Oct] (Box 48, Folder 993)
        FRKF 1385
      - Duplay, Maurice, [1910 ca. Sep 8] (Box 48, Folder 994)
        FRKF 958
      - Faure-Biguet, J.-N. (Jacques-Napoléon), [1922 Jun 9 or 10] (Box 48, Folder 995)
        FRKF 353
      - Gallimard, Gaston, [1922 early Jan] (Box 48, Folder 996)
        FRKF 1379
      - Ghéon, Henri, [1914-ca.1922] (Box 48, Folder 997)
        FRKF 938.1-3
      - Hahn, Reynaldo, [ca. 1906]-[ca. 1912], n.d. (Box 48, Folder 998)
        FRKF 172
        FRKF 253
        FRKF 502
        FRKF 702
        FRKF 730.3
        FRKF 1214
        FRKF 1215
        FRKF 1216
        FRKF 1217
        FRKF 1218
      - Halévy, Daniel, [1888?-1914] (Box 48, Folder 999-1001)
        FRKF 856
        FRKF 857
        FRKF 858
        FRKF 859
        FRKF 860
        FRKF 900.1
        FRKF 940
        FRKF 943
      - Hayman, Laure, [1906], [1922] (Box 48, Folder 1002)
        FRKF 170
        FRKF 1223
      - Humières, Robert, vicomte d', [1899 Feb 2] (Box 48, Folder 1003)
        FRKF 1373
      - Iturri, Gabriel, [1905 Jun 29] (Box 48, Folder 1004)
        FRKF 195
      - Lauris, Georges de, [1909], [1910] (Box 49, Folder 1005)
        FRKF 1219
        FRKF 1220
      - Levadé, Charles, 1894 Dec 25 (Box 49, Folder 1006)
        FRKF 96
      - Montesquiou-Fézensac, Robert, comte de, [1894-1921] (Box 49, Folder 1007)
        FRKF 206
        FRKF 207
        FRKF 360
        FRKF 701
        FRKF 730.2
        FRKF 1213
        FRKF 1224
        FRKF 1404
      - Mourey, Gabriel, [ca. 1905 Jul 12] (Box 49, Folder 1008)
        FRKF 359
      - Nahmias, Albert, [1912]-19, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1009)
        FRKF 171
      - Orléans, Pierre d', [ca. 1899 Nov 30] (Box 49, Folder 1010)
        FRKF 1372
      - Peter, René, [ca. 1911 Dec 30?] (Box 49, Folder 1011)
        FRKF 671
      - Porel, Jacques, [1919] (Box 49, Folder 1012)
        FRKF 738.1-2
      - Proust, Jeanne Weill, [1887]-[1905], n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1013-1015)
        Includes Les plaisirs et les jours, draft fragment, n.d.
        Includes letter with postcript by Madame Nathé Weil
        FRKF 137
        FRKF 167
        FRKF 340
        FRKF 670a
        FRKF 670c
        FRKF 736
        FRKF 1222
      - Proust, Jeanne Weill (to Marcel Proust), [1888]-[1903], n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1016)
        FRKF 193
        FRKF 670b
      - Réjane, [1919 Jul?] (Box 49, Folder 1017)
        FRKF 737
      - Rosny, J.-H. (1856-1940), [1921 Nov or Dec] (Box 49, Folder 1018)
        FRKF 1387
      - Scheikévitch, Marie, [1921 Jun 25] (Box 49, Folder 1019)
        FRKF 789
      - Sert, Misia, [1919 May 5] (Box 49, Folder 1020)
        FRKF 739
      - Straus, Geneviève, [ca. 1906 May 9] (Box 49, Folder 1021)
        FRKF 861
      - Straus, Geneviève (to Proust), 1920-[22], n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1022)
        FRKF 939
      - Vandérem, Fernand, [1920 Jan 15] (Box 49, Folder 1023)
        FRKF 254
      - Vaudoyer, Jean-Louis, [1910 Jul 18] (Box 49, Folder 1024)
        FRKF 1221
      - Weil, Nathé, Madame, [1885 or 1886, summer] (Box 49, Folder 1025)
        FRKF 168
        See also: Proust, Jeanne Weill, box 49, folders 1013-1015
      - Yturri, Gabriel
        See: Iturri, Gabriel, box 48, folder 1004
      - Other correspondents, [1880]-[1920], n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1026)
        FRKF 166
        FRKF 174
        FRKF 1212
        FRKF 1376
      - Unidentified, [1922], n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1027)
        FRKF 196
        FRKF 1380
    - WRITINGS
      - A la recherche du temps perdu (novel)
        See: A l'ombre des jeunes filles en fleurs (novel), Bsd, folder 2085
        See: Le côté de Guermantes (novel), box 285, folder 1627
        See: Du côté de chez Swann (novel), box 49, folder 1028
        See: La prisonnière (novel), box 49, folder 1030
      - A l'ombre des jeunes filles en fleurs (novel)
        Proof fragments, corrected, and draft
        - fragments, n.d.
          FRKF 157
          FRKF 190.1-3
          FRKF 235
          FRKF 444
          FRKF 498
          FRKF 741
          FRKF 1208
          FRKF 1209
          FRKF 1225
      - Le côté de Guermantes (novel)
        - Galley proofs, corrected, 1919
          FRKF 188
      - Du côté de chez Swann (novel)
        - "Le roman de l'inconscient": draft for an interview with E. J. Bois, [1913] (Box 49, Folder 1028)
          FRKF 1375
      - Les plaisirs et les jours (novel)
        See also: Correspondence/Proust, Jeanne Weill, box 49, folder 1013-1015
        - "Fragments de comédie italienne": drafts, [ca. 1895-96] (Box 49, Folder 1029)
          FRKF 942
      - La prisonnière (novel)
        - Draft fragment, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1030)
          FRKF 1378
      - Other writings
        - "Lettre de recommandation à Madame Urgèle, fée, pour Mr. Daniel Halévy, artiste dramatique", [ca. 1888 May 14] (Box 49, Folder 1031)
          FRKF 941
        - "La mort d'une grand-mère", [1907] (Box 49, Folder 1032)
          FRKF 1374
        - Notes on an article by Reynaldo Hahn, [1908?] (Box 49, Folder 1033)
          FRKF 677
        - Poems, [1887]-[1909], n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1034)
          Contents:
          "A Daniel Halévy, en le regardant pendant le premier quart d'heure de colle": with annotations by Halévy FRKF 946
          "A Wafflard, Brack ou Collardeau..." FRKF 1210
          "Chanson sur Robert" FRKF 788
          "Hélas seul de tant d'illustres..." FRKF 1070
          "Sonnet: En pensant à Daniel pendant qu'on marque les absents" FRKF 945.2
          "Sonnet: Pédérastie" FRKF 945.1
        - Le roman épistolaire: fragments in the hands of Proust and Daniel Halévy (Box 49, Folder 1035)
          FRKF 857z
        - "Sentiments filiaux d'un parricide," clipping, Le Figaro, [1907 Feb 1] (Box 49, Folder 1036)
          In a scrapbook with clippings of articles by others
        - Sésame et les lys (translation of John Ruskin, Sesame and lilies ): fragments
          FRKF 1418
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - Halévy, Daniel. "Une peine abimait..." (poem): holograph, with corrections by Proust, [ca. 1887] (Box 49, Folder 1037)
        FRKF 944
      - Levine, David. Caricature of Proust: proof, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 1038)
  - Puccini, Giacomo
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Forzano, Giovacchino, 1916 Jun 5 (Box 49, Folder 1039)
        FRKF 1073
      - Magrini, Angelo, 1918-24, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1040-1042)
        FRKF 994
      - Magrini, Angelo (from other correspondents), 1916-24, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1043)
      - Magrini, Angelo (from unidentified), 1918-28, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1044)
        Includes a postcard photograph of Puccini
      - Magrini, Erminia, 1921 Jan-Aug (Box 49, Folder 1045)
        See also: Magrini, Erminia (from Angelo Magrini), box 49, folder 1046
      - Magrini, Erminia (from Angelo Magrini), 1923-24 (Box 49, Folder 1046)
        Includes postcard inscribed by Puccini Includes letter with postscript from Fosca Puccini
      - Magrini, Erminia (from other correspondents), 1918-23, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1047)
      - Magrini family (other correspondence and documents), 1917-18, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1048)
      - Mugnone, Leopoldo, 1897 Feb 17 (Box 50, Folder 1049)
        FRKF 333
      - Nomellini, Plinio, 1903-[17], n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1050)
        FRKF 843
      - Puccini, Antonio (to Angelo Magrini), 1924-25, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1051)
        Includes letter also signed by Giuseppe Adami
      - Puccini, Elvira (to Angelo Magrini), 1923-24 (Box 50, Folder 1052)
      - Puccini, Elvira (to Erminia Magrini), 1928 Jul 31 (Box 50, Folder 1053)
      - Puccini, Elvira (to Alfredo Vandini)
        See: Vandini, Alfredo, box 50, folder 1066
      - Puccini, Fosca (to Angelo Magrini), 1924 Nov-Dec (Box 50, Folder 1054)
      - Seligman, Sybil, 1908-09 (Box 50, Folder 1055)
        FRKF 398
        FRKF 792
      - Tamagno, Francesco, 1888-92 (Box 50, Folder 1056)
        FRKF 1109
      - Vandini, Alfredo, 1893-1924 (Box 50, Folder 1057-1065)
        Includes postcards with photographs of Puccini, Villino Puccini, Boscolungo-Abetone, and scenes from La bohème and Tosca Includes postcard signed by Elvira Puccini
        FRKF 707
      - Vandini, Alfredo (Box 50, Folder 1066)
      - Vaucaire, Maurice, 1906 Aug 8 (Box 50, Folder 1067)
        FRKF 290
      - Other correspondents, [1897]-1923, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1068)
      - Other third party correspondence, 1920, 1923 (Box 50, Folder 1069)
        Includes postcard illustrating a scene from Turandot
    - MUSIC
      - La fanciulla del West (opera)
        - Sketches, n.d.
          FRKF 989
        - Fragment, n.d.
          FRKF 282
      - Inno a Diana (song)
        - Score, 1897 Dec 12
          FRKF 6
      - Madama Butterfly (opera)
        - Act 2, part 1: draft fragment in short score, n.d.
          FRKF 573
        - "Addio, fiorito asil," drafts in short score, [1904]
          FRKF 1040
      - Tosca (opera)
        - Act 3: draft fragment in short score, n.d.
          FRKF 1026
      - Turandot (opera)
        - Sketches, n.d.
          FRKF 989.5
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - Notes and ephemera, 1893-[20], n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1070)
        FRKF 734
      - Photographs of Puccini, [1903], n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1071)
      - Photographs of Puccini's funeral, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1072)
  - Radiguet, Raymond
    - WRITINGS
      - Le bal du comte d'Orgel (novel): typescript carbon, typed by Georges Auric, [ca. 1922] (Box 51, Folder 1073-1075)
        FRKF 1296
      - Les joues en feu (poems): fragments, typescript and holograph, with notes by Jean Cocteau (Box 51, Folder 1076)
        FRKF 1245.A03
      - Les joues en feu (poems): cover and title page maquettes, and galley proofs, corrected by Jean Cocteau, 1925 Mar 7 (Box 51, Folder 1077)
        FRKF 796.1
      - "Tohu" (story), n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1078)
        FRKF 189
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - Clippings about Radiguet, 1954, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1079)
        FRKF 1245.supp A
  - Ravel, Maurice
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Bennett, Arnold, 1920 May 21 (Box 51, Folder 1080)
        FRKF 212
      - [Bonniot, Edmond?], 1916 Jun 21 (Box 51, Folder 1081)
        FRKF 7
      - Calvocoressi, M. D. (Michel D.)
        See: Godebska, Ida, box 51, folders 1090-1095
      - Casella, Alfredo, 1914 Jul-Aug (Box 51, Folder 1082)
        FRKF 1110
      - Casella, Alfredo (from unidentified), [1916 Oct 17] (Box 51, Folder 1083)
      - Casella, Hélène Kahn, 1913-[37] (Box 51, Folder 1084-1086)
        Includes letter also signed by Gérard Hekkins
      - Delage, Maurice
      - Diaghilev, Serge, 1917 Jan 12 (Box 51, Folder 1087)
        FRKF 308
      - Evans, Edwin, 1910-14 (Box 51, Folder 1088)
        FRKF 1014
        FRKF 1015
        FRKF 1016
        FRKF 1017
        FRKF 1059
      - Fargue, Léon-Paul
      - Ghys, Henry, Madame, 1912, 1914 (Box 51, Folder 1089)
        FRKF 726a
      - Godebska, Ida, 1905-30, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1090-1095)
        Includes letters also signed by: Calvocoressi, M. D. (Michel D.) Delage, Maurice Fargue, Léon-Paul Samazeuilh, G. (Gustave)
        FRKF 25
      - Godebski, Jean, 1913 Apr 12 (Box 51, Folder 1096)
        FRKF 24
      - Godebski, Xavier Cyprian, 1908-27, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 1097-1099)
      - Hekkins, Gérard
        See: Casella, Hélène Kahn, box 51, folders 1084-1086
      - Hirt, Franz Josef, 1927 Jan 23 (Box 51, Folder 1100)
        FRKF 481
      - Jean-Aubry, G. (Georges), 1907-28 (Box 52, Folder 1101-1102)
        FRKF 289a-b
        FRKF 546
        FRKF 547
        FRKF 558c
        FRKF 726b
        FRKF 777.1-3
        FRKF 840
        FRKF 1060
        FRKF 1072
        FRKF 1135
        FRKF 1136
      - Jobert, Jean, 1922-28 (Box 52, Folder 1103)
        FRKF 238
      - Joubert, Joseph, 1913 May 5 (Box 52, Folder 1104)
        FRKF 21
      - Jourdan-Morhange, Hélène, 1922, 1923 (Box 52, Folder 1105)
        FRKF 1122
        FRKF 1123
      - Mahler, Alma, 1920 Aug 30 (Box 52, Folder 1106)
        FRKF 1154
      - Mignan, Edouard, 1923 Jun 20 (Box 52, Folder 1107)
        FRKF 531
      - Rabaud, Henri, 1922 Apr 19 (Box 52, Folder 1108)
        FRKF 1061
      - Roland-Manuel, 1913-24 (Box 52, Folder 1109)
        FRKF 1185
        FRKF 1186
        FRKF 1188
        FRKF 1189
        FRKF 1190
        FRKF 1191
        FRKF 1192
        FRKF 1193
      - Samazeuilh, G. (Gustave)
      - Sert, Misia, 1906-21 (Box 52, Folder 1110)
        FRKF 25.5
        FRKF 388
        FRKF 992
      - Other correspondents, 1905-31 (Box 52, Folder 1111)
        FRKF 154
        FRKF 176
        FRKF 548.1-2
        FRKF 1071
        FRKF 1187
      - Unidentified, 1916, [1922?] (Box 52, Folder 1112)
        FRKF 213
        FRKF 296
    - MUSIC
      - A la manière de--. Borodine (piano)
        - Music for piano, n.d.
          FRKF 1041
      - A la manière de--. Chabrier (piano)
        - Music for piano, n.d.
          FRKF 515
      - Berceuse sur le nom de Gabriel Fauré (violin and piano)
        - Score, 1922 Sep
          FRKF 1114
      - Un grand sommeil noir (song)
        - Score, 1895 Aug 6
          FRKF 869
      - Sites auriculaires (two pianos)
        - Score, [1895-97]
          FRKF 863
      - Sonata, violin, piano (1927)
        - Draft fragment, 1927 May
          FRKF 153
      - Arrangements
        - Debussy, Claude, Dances, piano ( Tarantelle styrienne ) orchestration: score, 1922 Dec
          FRKF 257
        - Debussy, Claude, Nocturnes. Nuages; Fêtes transcription for piano, 4 hands: score
          FRKF 256
        - Debussy, Claude, Pour le piano. Sarabande orchestration: score, 1922 Nov
          FRKF 258
        - Debussy, Claude, Prélude à l'après-midi d'un faune transcription for piano, 4 hands: score
          FRKF 255
        - Mussorgsky, Modest Petrovich, Khovanshchina orchestration: score fragments, [1913]
          FRKF 3
      - Unidentified
        See: Un grand sommeil noir, box 332, folder 1884
      - Exercises
        - "Sujet de Reber," fugue on a theme by Reber: score, 1900 May 31
          FRKF 864
    - WRITINGS
      - Letter to Le Figaro, [1911] (Box 52, Folder 1113)
        FRKF 26
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - Photographs of Ravel, c1914, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1114)
        FRKF 394
  - Raven-Hill, L. (Leonard)
    - DRAWINGS
      - "Exhausted Stalker: 'Oh, Shoot the Darn Stag Yourself!'" (cartoon): in pen-and-ink
        FRKF 99
  - Respighi, Ottorino
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      All materials, unless otherwise noted: FRKF 1337
      - Diaghilev, Serge, 1917 Aug 29 (Box 52, Folder 1115)
        FRKF 309
      - Fino, Giuseppe, 1912-14 (Box 52, Folder 1116)
      - Fino-Savio, Chiarina, 1911-16 Jun (Box 52, Folder 1117-1125)
      - Fino-Savio, Chiarina, 1916 Jul-32 (Box 52, Folder 1126-1128)
      - Fino-Savio, Chiarina (from other correspondents), 1921, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1129)
      - Fino-Savio, Chiarina (envelopes only), 1911-25 (Box 52, Folder 1130)
      - Other correspondents, 1914-29 (Box 52, Folder 1131)
    - MUSIC
      Includes music formerly owned by Chiarina Fino-Savio
      - Antiche cantate d'amore
        - Al tramontar del giorno, version for voice and piano: score
          Transcription of music by Bernardo Pasquini
          FRKF 1338.3
        - Quanta invidia mi fai, arrangement for soprano and string orchestra: short and full scores, and parts, 1917, n.d.
          Transcription of music by Benedetto Marcello Parts mostly in copyist's manuscript
          FRKF 1338.4
      - Liriche (1917) (songs)
        - La fine: score, n.d.
          FRKF 1338
      - Melodies (songs)
        - Abbandono: vocal line
          FRKF 1338.1
      - Prelude, organ
        - Prelude on a chorale by Johann Sebastian Bach: organ music, 1912 Jun
          FRKF 155
      - Re Enzo (opera)
        - Part for Lauretta: short score in copyist's manuscript, annotated by Respighi, [ca. 1905]
          FRKF 1338.2
      - Unidentified
        See: Arrangements/Chopin, box 333, folder 1900
      - Arrangements
        - Borodin, Aleksandr Porfirevich, Arabskaia melodiia orchestration: score, 1920
          FRKF 122.01
        - Chopin, Frédéric, Polonaise, op. 40, no. 1 orchestration: score, n.d.
          Includes unidentified fragment
          FRKF 122.02
        - Glinka, Mikhail Ivanovich, Ruslan i Liudmila orchestration: score, 1920 Mar
          Includes Rimsky-Korsakov, Nikolay, Sadko (Opera). Pesnia indiiskogo
          FRKF 122.03
          FRKF 122.06
        - Moszkowski, Moritz, Stücke, op. 57. Waltz orchestration: score, 1920 Sep 2
        - Paisiello, Giovanni, La serva padrona arrangement: short score, with annotations by Serge Diaghilev, n.d.
          FRKF 298.5
        - Paisiello, Giovanni, La serva padrona arrangement: full score, 1920 Mar
          Stamp of Serge Lifar
          FRKF 298
        - Rimsky-Korsakov, Nikolay, Orientale orchestration: score, n.d.
          FRKF 122.04
        - Rimsky-Korsakov, Nikolay, Sadko (Opera)
          See: Glinka, Mikhail Ivanovich, box 333, folder 1901
        - Spendiarov, Alek'sandr, Canzone tartara orchestration: score, 1920 May
          FRKF 122.07
        - Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich, Vremena goda, orchestration of excerpts: score, 1920 Mar
          FRKF 122.08
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - Note, [1938?] (Box 52, Folder 1132)
        FRKF 122
  - Ridgewell, William
    - DRAWINGS
      - "'Ere, Bill, Go a Bit Steady! That Sounded More Like 'Iccups!..." (cartoon): in pen-and-ink
        FRKF 100
  - Rimbaud, Arthur
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Bourde, Paul (to Rimbaud), 1888 Feb 29 (Box 52, Folder 1133)
        FRKF 247
      - Rimbaud family, 1884, 1885 (Box 52, Folder 1134)
        FRKF 246
        FRKF 1277
  - Robert, Louis de
    - WRITINGS
      - Papa (novel), 1895
        FRKF 653a
  - Robin, Louis
    Papers of Louis Robin relating to Francis de Croisset
    All materials: FRKF 1412
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Croisset, Francis de (to Robin), [1901]-36, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1135-1143)
      - Croisset, Francis de (to Robin), n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1144)
      - Croisset, Germaine de (to Robin), n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1145)
      - Ricou, Georges (to Robin), 1912-32, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1146)
      - Other correspondents (to and from Robin), 1958-62 (Box 53, Folder 1147)
      - Transcripts of letters, with notes, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1148-1150)
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - Clippings about Croisset, 1902-54, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1151)
      - Croisset, Francis de, Le tour de main (play): fragment, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1152)
      - Photographs of Croisset, [1910], n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1153)
        Includes photographs with: Bischoffsheim, née Chevigné, Marie-Thérèse Mistral, Frédéric Richepin, Jean
      - Other printed material about Croisset, 1905-33, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1154)
      - Original folders, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1155)
  - Rolfe, Frederick
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Unidentified, 1909 Nov 7 (Box 54, Folder 1156)
        FRKF 270
  - Rops, Félicien
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Unidentified, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1157)
        FRKF 663
  - Rossini, Gioacchino
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      Colbran, Isabella
      See: Sampieri, Francesco, box 54, folders 1159-1161
      - Moscheles, Ignaz, 1842 Sep 10 (Box 54, Folder 1158)
        FRKF 22
      - Sampieri, Francesco, [1821]-46, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1159-1161)
        Includes letter from Isabella Colbran to Rossini
        FRKF 729
      - Sampieri, Francesco (from Isabella Colbran), [ca. 1840] (Box 54, Folder 1162)
    - MUSIC
      - Cantata per Francesco I imperatore d'Austria
        - Score, [1819]
          FRKF 1042
          FRKF 1042a
      - Scherzo, piano, A minor
        - Music for piano, 1850 Jun 30
          FRKF 990
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - Photograph of Rossini, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1163)
        FRKF 699
  - Rostand, Edmond
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Bernhardt, Sarah, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1164)
        FRKF 674b
        FRKF 716a
      - Coquelin, Constant, [1899] (Box 54, Folder 1165)
        FRKF 711
    - WRITINGS
      - "La première de L'aiglon," written by an unidentified actor, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1166)
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - Ticket concerning "Dix Siècles de Livres français", [1949?] (Box 54, Folder 1166a)
        Removed from: Edmond Rostand, L'Aiglon (Paris: Librairie Charpentier et Fasquelle: Eugène Fasquelle, éditeur, 1900), call number Koch 33
        FRKF 674a
  - Rostand, Maurice
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Mercereau, Monsieur, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1167)
  - Roussel, Albert
    - MUSIC
      - Padmâvatî (opera ballet)
        - Act 2: sketches in short score, n.d.
          FRKF 556
      - Le testament de la tante Caroline (opera)
        - Short score, n.d.
          FRKF 708
  - Rubinstein, Anton
    - MUSIC
      - Quartet, strings, op. 106, No. 1
        - Score, n.d.
          FRKF 12
  - Rudolf, Crown Prince of Austria
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Pausinger, Joseph von, 1888 Sep 13 (Box 54, Folder 1168)
        FRKF 1309
  - Sachs, Maurice
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Unidentified, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1169)
        FRKF 462
  - Saint-Georges, Henri
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Halévy, F., n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1170)
        FRKF 681.18
  - Saint-Saëns, Camille
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Astruc, Gabriel, [1908 Jul 3] (Box 54, Folder 1171)
        FRKF 795.01
      - Audran, Edmond, 1896 May 8 (Box 54, Folder 1172)
        FRKF 1125
      - Augé de Lassus, Lucien, 1887-1913, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1173-1175)
        FRKF 795.07
      - Augé de Lassus, Lucien, Madame, 1905-21 (Box 54, Folder 1176-1177)
      - Bloch, [Ernest?], 1914 Feb 19 (Box 54, Folder 1178)
        FRKF 505
      - Cavaillé-Coll, Aristide, 1890 Oct 6 (Box 54, Folder 1179)
        FRKF 795.02
      - Clemenceau, Georges, 1920 Apr 13 (Box 54, Folder 1180)
        FRKF 656
      - Dandelot, Arthur, 1911-[21] (Box 54, Folder 1181)
        FRKF 795.03
      - Fauchey, Paul, [1907], 1918 (Box 54, Folder 1182)
        FRKF 795.04
      - Geslin, Gabriel, [1894]-[1909?], n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1183)
        FRKF 795.05
      - Gunsbourg, Raoul, 1915 Oct 22 (Box 54, Folder 1184)
        FRKF 795.06
      - Hahn, Reynaldo, 1906-21 (Box 54, Folder 1185)
        FRKF 657b
      - Herleroy, Marguerite, 1910-21, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1186-1188)
      - Heyman, Henry, Sir, 1915-19 (Box 54, Folder 1189)
        FRKF 13.5
      - Le Borne, Fernand, 1902-1911, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 1190)
        FRKF 1173
        FRKF 1174
        FRKF 1175
        FRKF 1176
      - Mary, Queen consort of George V, King of Great Britain, 1913 Mar 6 (Box 54, Folder 1191)